sogosurvey.com 2016-05-27

# Privacy Policy | SoGoSurvey

SoGoSurvey is an application service provider that provides you, our customer, tools to conduct two-way communications with your customers, employees, suppliers and constituents. Like the postal service, we understand that the Information we deliver belongs to you and your survey participants, not us. At SoGoSurvey, it is a core business principle that we must protect the privacy of our customers and survey participants or we will not have either. With this principle in mind, SoGoSurvey created this privacy policy to demonstrate our commitment to your privacy.

You should be assured that our practices stated in this policy are practiced worldwide. SoGoSurvey is a global organization, with legal entities, business processes, management structures, and technical systems that cross borders. We may share information between SoGoSurvey entities and transfer it to offices around the world. Some countries may provide less legal protection for personal information than the country in which the information was provided. No matter the country standards, we will still handle the information in the manner we describe here.

This Privacy Policy applies only to information collected on our web site and domain at the URL [http://www.sogosurvey.com](http://www.sogosurvey.com/)(the "Site") and our SoGoSurvey service platform,owned and operated by SoGoSurvey LLC. It does not speak for SoGoSurvey practices for information collected elsewhere or the practices of any third parties, including those of our partners who may display SoGoSurvey branding on their sites. It also describes the choices available to you regarding the use of, your access to, and how to update and correct your personal information.

If you have questions about this privacy policy please email, [privacy@sogosurvey.com](mailto:privacy@sogosurvey.com)

##### 1\. What Information do we collect?

SoGoSurvey collects information about both you, our customers ("Customers", "Client" or "you") and the individuals who participate in, or are invited to participate in, any of your surveys ("Survey Participants"). Collectively, the information collected about you ("Customer Information") and Survey Participants ("Participant Information") are referred to as "Information".

Customer Information: When Customers register on the Site, we ask you to give us name and contact information: company name, name of contact, title of contact, company address, telephone number, email address, user name and password, and billing information which may include credit card numbers. Customers also provide us with Information regarding the Services you have ordered (e.g., the number of surveys Customers will pay for or whether you want a private or public survey). In addition to the Information you knowingly provide, we also know when and how often you log on to the Site. (See “Tracking Technologies” below).

Participant Information: We receive Participant Information from both Customers and Survey Participants. You provide us with the email address, and sometimes the name, of each Participant. Before receiving such Information, we contractually require that you warranty that you have a pre-existing relationship with the Survey Participant and/or the Survey Participant's permission to receive electronic messages. Survey Participants provide us with the Information requested by you, for example, their gender or zip code, as well as all answers to the survey questions. Customers are solely responsible for the content of the surveys and we do not control the theme or questions asked in any survey. In order to enhance survey response rates, we record: (i) if and when a Survey Participant has responded to a survey and (ii) if and when a Survey Participant has received a reminder. In addition, we receive any Information contained in any communications a Survey Participant makes directly with SoGoSurvey. (See “Tracking Technologies” below).

You can log in to our site using sign-in services such as Facebook Connect or an Open ID provider. These services will authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain personal information with us such as your name and email address to pre-populate our sign up form. Services like Facebook Connect give you the option to post information about your activities on this Web site to your profile page to share with others within your network. 

Our Web site includes a Social Media Features such as the Facebook button. This Feature may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. This Feature is hosted by Facebook. Your interactions with this Feature are governed by Facebook’s privacy policy.

If you choose to use our referral service on SoGoSurvey to share an article from our site, we will ask you for your email address and your friend’s email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email in your name inviting him or her to visit the site to review the article. SoGoSurvey does not store this information and uses it for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email.

##### 2\. SoGoSurvey Platform Policy 

The use of Information collected through our service shall be limited to the purpose of providing the service for which the Client has engaged SoGoSurvey.

SoGoSurvey collects Information under the direction of its Clients, on its service platform and has no direct relationship with the individuals whose personal data it processes. If you are a customer of one of our Clients and would no longer like to be contacted by one of our Clients that use our service, please contact the Client that you interact with directly.

SoGoSurvey works with its Clients to help them provide notice to their customers concerning, the purpose for which personal Participant Information is collected.

SoGoSurvey has no direct relationship with the individuals whose personal data it processes. An individual who seeks access, or who seeks to correct, amend, or delete inaccurate data should direct his query to SoGoSurvey’s Client (the data controller). If the Client requests SoGoSurvey to remove the data, we will respond to their request within 30 days. We may transfer certain limited personal information, such as a Client’s name or payment information, to third party companies solely so they can help us provide our services. SoGoSurvey does not Transfer Survey Participant or Client’s Information to third parties, other than for supporting services.

We will retain Survey Participant or Client’s Information data we process on behalf of our Clients for as long as needed to provide services to our Client. SoGoSurvey will retain this Information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

Tracking Technologiesemployed on the Site and the Services Platforms

As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information may include Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data.

We do not link this automatically collected data to other information we collect about you.

SoGoSurvey and our partners, marketing partners, affiliates, analytic companies, or service providers, such as billing and customer support providers, use technologies such as cookies, beacons, tags, and scripts, to analyze trends, administer the website, tracking users’ movements around the website, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by the companies referenced above on an aggregated or individualized basis.

We use cookies for our shopping cart,upgrades to purchases to remember users’ settings, for authentication. Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. If you reject cookies, you may still use our website, but your ability to use some features or areas of our website may be limited.

We partner with a third party to either display advertising on our website or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our third party partner may use technologies such as cookies to gather information about your activities on this website and other sites in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you interest-based ads, you may opt-out by clicking [here](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/) (or if located in the European Union click [here](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/) ). Please note this does not opt you out of being served ads. You may continue to receive generic ads.

Third parties with whom we partner to provide certain features on our website or to display advertising based upon your web browsing activity also use Flash cookies or HTML5 to collect and store information. Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing HTML5. To manage Flash cookies, please click here: <http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html>

Widgets

From time to time our site includes Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the third party company providing the Feature.

Newsletter(s)

If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter(s), we will use your name and email address to send the newsletter to you. You may choose to stop receiving our newsletter or marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails, accessing the email preferences in your account settings page, or you can contact us at [unsubscribe@SoGoSurvey.com](mailto:unsubscribe@SoGoSurvey.com)

Blogs/Forums

If you use a blog or forum on this site, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums.

Testimonials

From time to time, we post customer testimonials on our web site which may contain personally identifiable information such as the customer's name. We do obtain the customer's consent prior to posting the testimonial to post their name along with their testimonial.

If you want to remove your personal information that is being displayed on our website under public pages please send your request to [privacy@sogosurvey.com](mailto:privacy@sogosurvey.com)

Import Contacts

You can import contacts from your Gmail or other address books to invite other individuals to become members of our website. We do not collect the username and password for the email account from which you wish to import your contacts, and we only collect the contact email address for contacts that your select for that purpose.

##### 3\. How Do We Use Information?

We use your Customer Information in the normal course of our business, including to contact you regarding technical support, discuss billing issues, or to bring to your attention any aspect of our mutual business. We may also use your contact information to provide you with policy or product updates or to introduce new products and services. If you do not wish to receive promotional emails from us, please follow the unsubscribe instructions included in each promotional email.

We will send you strictly service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email. Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature.

All Participant Information resides in our database primarily for the benefit of you, our Customers. At your direction, we use a Survey Participant's email address (and perhaps name) to send survey invitations and reminders. We also use Participant Information to improve the performance of our Site and services by analyzing site and user behavior, troubleshooting technical problems, resolving disputes and address complaints, and verifying compliance with the Terms of Service.

If SoGoSurvey intends to use any Information in a manner that deviates from this Privacy Policy we will provide notice of how we intend to use that Information as we collect it. The use of that specific Information will be used solely as stated in the alternative disclosure.

Data Retention

We will retain Information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

Links to Other Sites

This site contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by SoGoSurvey. Please be aware that we, SoGoSurvey, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information.

##### 4\. With Whom Do We Share Information?

We do not share the Information with any third parties except under the following very limited circumstances:

  1. Participant Information with Customer: Our business is the provision of tools that allow you, our Customer, to conduct meaningful surveys with your employees, suppliers, customers and constituents. Accordingly, we provide you with access to the Participant Information given in response to the surveys you have conducted. You may use the Participant Information consistent with your own privacy policy and applicable law.
  2. As You Explicitly Allow: We may share or otherwise use your Customer Information as you explicitly allow us and we may share Participant Information as both you and the Survey Participant expressly allow. For example, you are given the opportunity to either hide or make available to Survey Participants certain Customer contact information in connection with any survey.
  3. Agents Acting on Our Behalf: We may share some of your Information with other companies who provide us with technical and other type of services such as a credit card processor. They will be contractually granted access to only that Information which is necessary for them to do their jobs and they will be prohibited from using the Information for any other purpose including marketing or sharing the Information with any other party. We do not share any personally identifiable information with third parties who are not services providers.
  4. For Legal Reasons: We may disclose your personal information as required by law such as to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims and when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others. We may also share your Information to investigate, prevent or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.
  5. Affiliates and Acquisition: If SoGoSurvey is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our website, of any change in ownership, uses of personal information, and choices you may have regarding your personal information. We may also disclose your personal information to any other third party with your prior consent. 

##### 5\. Can the Information be Changed?

Your Customer Information may be viewed and modified in our active database in real-time at any time. If you wish to request deletion of data from our site, please contact us at [support1@sogosurvey.com](mailto:support1@sogosurvey.com). The changed Information may remain in archives and records for some period of time. Once a Survey Participant has submitted a survey, the Survey Participant will not be able to access his Information through the Site. Survey Participants may contact you and you, in turn, will be able to view the Survey Participant's collected Information and, where appropriate, work with us in modifying such Information. If the client requests SoGoSurvey to remove the Survey Participant’s data or the Client’s data, SoGoSurvey will respond to their Client’s request within 30 business days.

##### 6\. How Is Information Protected?

Our Site has substantial and elaborate security measures in place to protect your Information. Unique user names and passwords must be entered each time a person logs on. The Site is hosted in a secure server environment that uses a firewall and other technology to reasonably prevent access from outside intruders. Internally, we use security-logs, train our employees and limit access to only essential personnel. When transmitting sensitive Information, we use encryption technology. All our technology and processes are not, however, guarantees of security. Please keep your user name and password secret and let us know at [privacy@sogosurvey.com](mailto:privacy@sogosurvey.com) if you learn or suspect that our security has been breached.

##### 7\. Changes in the Privacy Policy:

As we are constantly improving our services and expanding our business, we retain the right to modify this privacy policy at any time. In the event we make such changes, we will announce the changes and post the new policy on the Site. Information collected after the new policy is posted will be used in conformance with the new policy. Information gathered under the old policy will continue to be used in conformance with that policy unless we, in conjunction with Customer, notify Survey Participants of the changes and the Survey Participant does not prohibit the use of the Information in conformance with the new policy. If we make any material changes we will notify you or our Client by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

##### TRUSTe Scope

The TRUSTe program covers only information that is collected through this domain, [www.sogosurvey.com](http://www.sogosurvey.com/) and our service platform. It does not cover information that may be collected through software downloaded from the website.

In order to view our relationship with TRUSTe, please visit the validation page visible by clicking on the TRUSTe seal. If you have unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact TRUSTe at [https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request.](https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request)

##### EU-US and Swiss-US Safe Harbor

SoGoSurvey complies with the U.S. – E.U. Safe Harbor framework and the U.S. - Swiss Safe Harbor framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal data from European Union member countries and Switzerland. SoGoSurvey has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view SoGo Survey’s certification, please visit [http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/.](http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/)

Additional Information

If you have questions about this Privacy Policy or the Site, you can contact us at [privacy@sogosurvey.com](mailto:privacy@sogosurvey.com)

Contact Us:  

2291 Wood Oak Dr #300

Herndon, VA 20171

USA

Last Updated: September 23, 2015
